We will move through Earth's horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
Let's fight for this blue sea and
let the wind take us far away.
Don't give up.
So I can come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this drop.
Sometimes we share.
Shut it up.
Do not be so afraid to podcast.
To have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times.
I'll try.
Look and breathe it out.
It's alright now.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to move them up.
We will move to our single horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We're a world for our heads.
We will win for sure.
Dreaming on.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the ones that
just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Become the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinite portions.
We will step up and we
will leave for sure.
So keep moving on.
All right, we'll leave it to you.
Please stay safe.
Do not worry on my behalf.
I give you my word.
I will take Lord Yasui and
return him to where he belongs.
He will be honorably laterest in Kuri.
Have a safe journey!
We are so grateful.
Thank you, sir.
It will be my pleasure.
This is the least that I can do to repay
the sacrifice he made for our cause,
after all.
We're all set.
Let's book it, Nami.
Kanjuro! Okay.
Yes, just a moment.
I'll be right with you.
Best of luck.
Safe travels to you.
Meanwhile, at a harbor between
the flower capital and Kuri...
The people you see here
are heinous criminals.
They made an attempt on Shogun
Orochi's life, then fled.
We've set up checkpoints
all around the capital.
Line up for your inspection.
Step forward and show your faces.
What should we do?
I had a feeling they might try this.
They wouldn't just let us go.
But there's only one way, Takuri.
We have to take that boat, don't we?
We're gonna need a genius
plan to pull this one off.
A curse upon you!
These poor people are haunted by a ghost!
Here we go, quickly please!
Well, somehow that worked.
How's otoko?
All tuckered out, exhausted
from all that crying. I'm sure.
I feel so bad.
I want to cheer her
up, but what can I say?
Don't leave me!
Please, daddy!
Please, you have to get up!
Bonkichi!
Let me take her!
Your bones are hard!
and likely cold, too.
How dare you?
They're not that cold, guys.
What? What?
It cannot be!
Ships! Ships! Ships!
I have been rendered
speechless. They're splendid.
Save your praise until
after we fix them up.
I pulled them here from
all across the country.
They were left at ports
that Kaido had destroyed.
They'll serve well for the raid.
We'll be able to transport
thousands of warriors to Onigashima.
You're quite dependable after all.
My opinion of you has improved.
Yes, mine has as well.
When did you, Gar, get so conscientious?
What did you expect?
You think I just slept for 20 years?
As for the ships, repairs will be easy.
We have Zerfranosuke after all.
This has been a long road, with
many an obstacle along the way.
But I feel it.
Freedom for 1-0 is within our sight.
i thought you took care of big
mom you dipshit do your damn
job i'm quite certain i knocked this
ship off the waterfall, brother.
Why did you bring our enemy here? Shut up!
Our comms were shut off in Udon.
What was I supposed to do?
King!
I'm willing to forgive your
extremely rude attack only
if you join me.
We have all sorts of people
living in my country.
Well, that is to say, all but three.
One of those races is
said to have died out.
So as you might imagine,
they're tough to find.
And yet, here you are.
I refuse.
Hmm.
Ma-ma-ma-ma.
Isn't that a shame? All right?
If you won't join me, uncuff me.
That's not how it works!
Are you crazy?
Hey, you guys.
Huh?
Did you know?
Big Mom and Commander Kaido used
to be in the same pirate crew!
Take those cuffs off now, fools.
What do you think you're doing?
Commander Kaido!
You showed up after all, Lin-Win.
It's been a while.
Kaido!
Hey, you dopes!
He told you to take these
handcuffs off! What?
I'm sure he was just joking!
That would be completely insane!
Take them off!
If you insist!
Why, it's been decades, hasn't it?
Napoleon!
Right here, Mama!
I'm so happy!
You're back to normal!
I'm shy around strangers,
so I didn't come out!
I said I would kill you if you came here.
If you think I came here to die,
you've got another thing coming!
Oh, my God.
Two-sword style, 7.20 caliber Phoenix!
You think fighting one storm will stop me?
This is ridiculous.
What is the point of all this?
Are you an ally or are you an enemy?
Who the hell are you?
Why do you need all these weapons?
What are you doing?
Waiting on this bridge
in the middle of nowhere?
Just give me back my sword
before I have to cut you,
like you said, one's not a loss for you.
And it's certainly not worth dying over.
Not that sword!
Any other blade I would let you take!
Shusui should have never been taken away!
It's an irreplaceable
treasure to this land!
Shusui?
That was the start of Wano's ruin
when this country lost Shusui!
It was a crime that enraged
our God of the Blade.
Each region was attacked one by one.
Then the country was
conquered by the enemy!
He wasn't a god!
Cease your blasphemy!
Stop fighting!
Is this some sort of performance piece?
Why would a samurai and a monk be
fighting each other in the snow?
It seems you're trying to spare each
other's lives rather than end them.
A fish man?
He's... alive!
Is that you, Kawamatsu?
How do you know my name?
Those two just keep going at it!
I think we'd better pull back to the
mainland. Hey, you! What the hell?
Your boss is out there kicking ass,
and you guys are in here cowering
and talking about running away?
Okay, but why are you here?
Were you gonna escape, too? Oh?
No.
What gave you that idea?
Uh, anyway, have you gotten
a call from Udon yet?
I'm afraid not, and we can't
reach them by smell, either.
Yes!
I'll go there and check
if everything's okay.
You're just trying to escape from here!
That's cheating!
I'll be right back.
I'm just popping in.
Give me that. Yes, sir. Sorry. Click.
What's up? This is Queen.
This is the Chief Warden.
It seems we finally got through.
Good.
That means you fixed the smells, I assume.
Yes, just a moment ago.
Well, as it turns out, I don't
need all these men here after all.
If you're shorthanded, how
about I make a trip back?
That's just another excuse for him to run!
Actually, that won't be necessary. Oh!
Rejected!
All of our enemies are
sitting quietly behind bars.
That includes Straw Hat, Luffy,
Captain Kidd, and all the other rebels.
Is that so?
I just called to let you
know that all is well.
Well, I wish it wasn't!
Now you're being pretty!
That's all from me.
Until next time.
I hope that I please you, my lady.
Did I do good? Mm-hmm.
Yes, that was perfect.
Who's a good boy?
I am.
What splendid sorcery.
She tamed her enemy with
a mere millet dumpling.
She can tame beasts, but also those
who have obtained beast powers.
Looks like everything
worked out in the end.
Hm, thanks to your
efforts, we are grateful.
How kind, but you're right.
I was rather clever, wasn't I?
After I gobbled up their boss snail,
their communications were cut.
That means no pesky
reinforcements for the enemy.
Oh, I can't wait.
On the day of the battle, they'll be
in for an ugly surprise, won't they?
So don't forget my
contributions to your cause.
We're in this together now, you and I.
For that, I'm glad.
Onward, with the smells working, let
us contact Keenemon and the others.
Sa tu Ramen.
I promise, we shall repay this
debt even if it costs us our lives.
It's fine coming, it wasn't
any trouble to beat that virus!
And your Samurai honor thing
is a bit much, so no thank you.
Well, at least it all worked out.
Luffy Tato's back in action.
We got this! You ready?
Yeah!
Luffy Daddy!
You're the man!
And he's kicking a few friends
left and right, like always.
All it took was a little
push from Lord Momonosuke,
and they came around.
I know that face.
Still has that aura about him, doesn't he?
How long has it been?
We missed you, boss Hyogoro.
Oh my, it's them!
Blood-riding Omasa!
Split-hat Tsunaguro!
Hojo the Pottle Gourd!
and snake eyes, yatape
leaders of the underground,
from all across the land, were right here.
This is an honor; I never thought
I'd live to serve you again.
The honor is mine; I'm so glad.
You're alive and well.
We're not worthy of your kindness,
yeah. You've got that. It's backwards.
It's taking a crap after a bath!
Yeah, what he said precisely, so?
What a bunch of weirdos!
These guys' hands are to you, old man?
Old man!
Whoa!
Now tear your nails!
Cover your toes!
Rip off your ears!
You'll pay in body parts for that!
What do you want us to take, boss?
And how many?
Just give us the word!
Don't take anything!
That man saved my life!
Put him down right now!
Don't you worry, boss.
If there are any rebels left,
we'll find them and bring them to your
side, no matter where they're hiding.
Splendid. Do your best. Yes, sir.
Seems you escaped death, kid. For today.
I hope you learned your lesson for
next time. Shut up! You're lame!
My word!
What a surprise!
To think you were the mystery man from
Kuri who stole Kaido's blueprints!
How fortunate!
Long have we searched for this!
The layout of the mansion on Onigashima!
A shame that I wasted so
much of Surfer Nosuke's time.
But now, we can plan our
attack on enemy territory!
What a reliable ally!
When did Yugar get so conscientious?
Are you gonna keep saying
that every time, dog?
Is that you, Race? What's the word?
Have you managed to rescue
Sir Luffy Daddy yet?
Indeed we have, but that
is only the beginning.
I'll spare you the details for now,
but we just recruited 3,500 warriors.
3,500 warriors?
That's no small number.
So you've not only saved
Sir Luffy as planned,
you've also freed Kawamatsu
and recruited an army?
Hold on, Kawamatsu is
locked in that prison?
You mean the entire region
is under your control now?
You've got to have achieved far
more than a rescue mission, Raizo.
Next stop!
Our friends are recruiting
even more allies as we speak,
however, with that comes a
complication which we must address.
This land has several weapons
factories, as you surely know,
but their products are intended for export
and do not stay in the
land of Wano for long.
Since our forces are mostly samurai,
they are skilled with swords and
spears, but as you can imagine,
those are difficult to
come by since Orochi
has banned citizens from carrying weapons,
no matter how many allies we have,
if they are not properly armed,
our plan is doomed to fail!
Very well, I understand
this is a serious matter.
What to do?
I shall give this
quandary some thought,
but I must go.
I'll inform.
of our group's accomplishments later.
For the time being, I will head to Amagasa
Village and gauge their preparedness.
Race, I look forward to sharing the
details of our mutual victories.
As do I.
Click.
And now, we depart.
I can scarcely believe my eyes,
But I'd know that face anywhere.
Kawamatsu!
It can't be.
Is that really you?
Kawamatsu!
It is you, to think I would
find you in a place like this.
But never mind, if you are
well, that's all that matters.
My heart leaps with joy to find you safe.
Lady Hiyori.
Oh yeah, that's right.
She said something about being raised
by a cop after her parents died.
Forgive me.
Back then, I only ran away
because I feared for your health.
Even if it was only a scrap, you always
gave me every morsel of food you found.
It appears that I am still
lacking as a samurai.
Kawamatsu!
I couldn't stand to watch you waste away,
especially knowing that you could
easily survive if you were alone.
I couldn't stand the thought
that you might die because of me.
I'm sorry for leaving you, Kawamatsu, but
if nothing is done, I fear you may die.
It was painful, but what could I do?
Dear Kawamatsu, thank you for everything.
I'll be fine, Hiyori.
Lady...
Lady Hiyori!
Your Majesty!
Would you believe it?
I washed my hair all by myself today!
All I had to do was close my eyes!
Not here.
Where to next?
Lady Hiyori!
Oh, Lady Hiyori, why'd you run away?
My lady, please.
Where did you go?
What have I done wrong, my lady?
Why?
Come back.
Lady Hiyori!
I'm so sorry.
You must have suffered.
Now I finally know why you ran away.
How kind of you to think of me.
Though thanks to that, I put
on quite a lot of weight.
Who goes there?
Your days are numbered, Kikimari!
You really think you could steal
our weapons and get away with it?
I'll take them back along
with everything else!
These are hunting rounds.
They take down things twice your size!
Hide behind that tree, my lady.
I shall.
Huh?
Are those buddies of his?
What does it matter?
Just shoot them all to death!
Go to hell!
Oh, oh!
Kappa style!
Two-sword style!
River of Retribution!
Rhino cycle!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Shikawa Matsu!
Ah!
Are you all right?
As long as you are, Lady Hiyori.
I can't believe it's you!
Hey, wait a sec!
Are you running away again?
Asshole!
Give me my sword!
Shikawa Matsu!
It's really you!
I'm so glad you're alive!
Thank you.